var questions = [
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `name` variable?',
    extras: 'question-1',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `age` variable?',
    extras: 'question-2',
    correct: 1,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `isPlantEater` variable?',
    extras: 'question-3',
    correct: 2,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `species` variable?',
    extras: 'question-4',
    correct: 3,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `details` variable?',
    extras: 'question-5',
    correct: 4,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is each item inside the array?',
    extras: 'question-6',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `height` property?',
    extras: 'question-7',
    correct: 1,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `swingTail` variable?',
    extras: 'question-8',
    correct: 5,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `console` variable?',
    extras: 'question-9',
    correct: 4,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `.log()` property?',
    extras: 'question-10',
    correct: 5,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: "What data type is the `'Smack!'` bit?",
    extras: 'question-11',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `elems` variable?',
    extras: 'question-12',
    correct: 3,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is stored inside the `elems[2]` item?',
    extras: 'question-13',
    correct: 4,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `.style` property?',
    extras: 'question-14',
    correct: 4,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  },
  {
    question: 'What data type is the `.backgroundColor` property?',
    extras: 'question-15',
    correct: 0,
    choices: [
      'String',
      'Number',
      'Boolean',
      'Array',
      'Object',
      'Function',
    ]
  }
];

MultipleChoice(ActivityRunner(), questions);
